Guide to the UE Research Department Personnel Papers, 1937-2001 UE.10.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
UE Research Department Personnel Papers
1937-2001
ULS Archives & Special Collections
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. Research Department
UE.10.1
6.67 Linear Feet (6 boxes)
The research department of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) was developed to gather information regarding companies and labor issues concerning the union. This subgroup contains the files of UE Executive Assistant and National Activities Director Lyle Dowling and UE Research Director Nat Spero, which include press releases, correspondence, and clippings regarding a variety of topics relating to the UE and the American labor movement.
History
The research department of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) was developed to gather information regarding companies and labor issues concerning the union. This information is used by UE locals and the national office to develop publications that inform members of any concerns affecting their workplace and reports used to assist in negotiating contracts with employers.
This subgroup is concerned with two members of the research department. Lyle Dowling served as UE Executive Assistant and National Activities Director from 1939-1942. Nathan "Nat" Spero served as the UE's Research Director from 1944 to 1983. Prior to his time with the union, Spero worked on projects for the United States' Department of Labor. In addition to his role in the research department, he was also involved in the UE national conventions and committees, as well as serving as editor of the UE Officer's Report from 1951 to 1982. After his time with the UE, Spero taught math and labor history at Queens College.
Scope and Content Notes
This subgroup contains the files of UE Executive Assistant and National Activities Director Lyle Dowling and UE Research Director Nat Spero. These records include press releases, correspondence, and clippings regarding a variety of topics relating to the UE and the American labor movement.
Arrangement
Subject files within each series are arranged alphabetically.
Series 10.1.1. Lyle Dowling
Series 10.1.2. Nathan Spero
Access Restrictions
No restrictions
Acquisition Information
Gift of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America on 1976 and 1986. Additional materials regarding Nathan Spero were donated by Jane LaTour in November 2006.
Previous Citation
UE Research Department Personnel Papers, 1937-2001, UE.10.1, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Related Material
Congress of Industrial Organizations Collection, 1938-1982, UE.10.2.2, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
All series in subgroup UE.10.2 are records of the UE Research Department on various topics.
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- United States -- History; Labor; Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.); Dowling, Lyle; Spero, Nathan; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
- Lyle Dowling, 1938-1942; 10.1.1.
  Scope and Contents note
  This subgroup contains some of the records of Lyle Dowling, UE Executive Assistant and National Activities Director from 1939-1942. The materials contained here are mostly Federated Press Releases, clippings from other publications, bulletins and correspondence. Communications from Dowling are typically between districts, the national office, and national UE officers such as James Matles, the Director of Organization.
  - ABC of Politics, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abbondi, Peter, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abrams, Caroline, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Accidents, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Active Photos, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Adi, Alexander, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Advance Printers, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Aerovox, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Affiliated Schools for Workers, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Affiliated Young Democrats, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "Against This War", 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Agrarian Problems, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "Agreement wiht G.E.", 1940 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Agricultural, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Air Associates, Inc., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Airplanes - Prices, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Albert, Johnny, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Aliens, 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Aliens-Discrimination, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Aliens-Registration, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "All Aid", 1941 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Allan, Lewis, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Allen, William, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Allis-Chalmers Strike, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Aluminum, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Aluminum Workers of America, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - American Association for Adult Education, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - American Communications Association, 1939-1942 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - American Farm Bureau, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - american Federation of Labor, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - American Federation of Labor - Convention, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - American Federation of Labor-Legislative, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - American Federation of Labor-Statements, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - American Federation of Labor v. Congress of Industrial Organization, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - American Federation of Labor v. National Labor Relations Board, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - American Institute of Public Opinions, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - American Investors' Union, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - American Irish Defense Association, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - American Labor Party - New York County, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - American Legion, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - American Newspaper Guild - Labor Press Unit, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - American Newspaper Guild - Lectures, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - AmericanProtestant Defense League, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - American Red Cross, 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - American Telephone and Telegraph, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Amidon, Beulah, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Anderson, Charles W., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Anderson, Franklin, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Anthracite Tri-District News, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Anti-Alien Laws, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Anti-Trust Case, undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Anti-Trust Indictments, 1939-1941 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Anti-Trust Suits, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Apex Hosiery Case, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Apprenticeship, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Appresnticeship-California, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Apprenticeship-California, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Apprenticeship-Plans, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Associated Farmers, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Associated Hospitals, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Associated Press, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Astoria Printers, undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Aviation Industry, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Austin, Warren, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Australia - Labor, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Bachrach, Marion, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Backmann, Henry, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Ball, Joseph, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Bambrick, James, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Bard, Ralph A., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Barrows, Robert, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Barry, Thomas, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Barry, Walter, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Barschoff, Paul, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Bassin, Frederick, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Batt, William, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Beal, Edwin, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Beals, Clyde, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Bean, Adelaide, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Beardsley, David, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Belenky, Allen, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Bell, J.R., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Bell Telephone Labs, undated (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Bennett, Harry, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Bentley, Gladys, undated (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Bentley, William, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Berenholtz, Anne, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Bergoff, Pearl, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Berte, Adolphe, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Bersing, Carl, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Bethlehem Case, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Besch, Peter, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Biberman, Herbert, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Biddle, Frances, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Bill of Rights, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Bioff Case, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Bittner, Van, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Bliss, Willard, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Block, Harry, 1939-1941 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Bloom, Frank, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Board of Elections, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Boland, John, undated (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Bollen, Donald, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Book Lists, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Boss, Adam, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Bostrom, Karl, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Boudin, Jean, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Boudin, Louis, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Boyer, Richard, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Brandon Films, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Braunlich, Arthur, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Bread and Butter, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Brentano, Inc., 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Bridges Case, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Bridges Defense Committee, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Bridges, Harry, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Brinton, Herbert, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Brooklyn Eagle, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Brophy, John, undated (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Brown, Mrs. Alfred, undated (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Brown, Elmer, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Brown, Harvey, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Bruno, H.A. and Associates, undated (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Byrnes, James F., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Buchmanism, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - "Build the CIO", 1940 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Building Manager, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Bullitt, William, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Burelles Press Clipping Bureau, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Burns, Frank, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Burrows, William G., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Business Week, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Butler, George, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Cadden, Joseph, 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Cahill, John T., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - California State Industrial Union Council, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Cammer, Harold, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Campbell, Matthew, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Canada, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Capital Strike, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Carmann, Joseph, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Carson, William, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Casey, Joseph, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - Catholic Church, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Catholic Policy, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Chambers, William, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - Chapman, Emanuel, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - Chapman, William, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - China, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Christian Social Action, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Chrysler - Airtemp, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - Church and Labor, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - CIO-Bills, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - CIO-Constitution, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - CIO-Convention, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - CIO-Convention Proceedings, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - CIO-Convention Draft Resolutions, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - CIO-Correspondence, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - CIO-DeCaux, Len, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - CIO-Diecasters, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - CIO-Draft State Legislation, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - CIO-Economic Outlook, 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - CIO-Executive Board, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - CIO-Fowler, C.W., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - CIO-Greater New York Industrial Union Council, 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - CIO-Haywood, Allen, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - CIO-Hetzel, Ralph Jr., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - CIO-Hudson County, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - CIO-Indiana State Industrial Union Council, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - CIO-International Longshoremen and Warehousemen's Union, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - CIO-International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - CIO-Legal Bulletin, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - CIO-Legislative, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - CIO-Legislative Promotion, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - CIO-Michigan, undated (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - CIO-Miscellaneous, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - CIO-Murray, Philip, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - CIO-National Conference of CIO Editors, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - CIO-National Committee for American and Allied War Relief, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - CIO-New Jersey, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - CIO-News, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - CIO-Newspaper Guild of New York, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - CIO-Officers, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - CIO-Pamphlets, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - CIO-Political Action, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - CIO-Pressman, Lee, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - CIO-Priorities Conference, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - CIO-Propaganda, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - CIO-Publications Department, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - CIO-Rochester, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - CIO-State, County and Municipal Workers, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - CIO-Transport Workers Union, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - CIO-United Automobile Workers, 1941-1942 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - CIO-United Office and Professional Workers, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - CIO-United Shoe Workers, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - CIO-United Steel Workers, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - CIO-Unity with A.F.L., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - CIO-UCAPAWA, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - CIO-Walsh, J. Raymond, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - CIO-Washington State, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - CIO-"CIO What It Is", 1939 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - CIO-Women's Auxiliaries, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - CIO-World's Fair, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Citrine, Walter, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Clark, Bennett, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Clason, Charles, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Classet, Gowell, 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Cleveland union Leader, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - "Cliveden Set", 1942 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Cohn, Sidney, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Collective Barganing Associates, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Colleges and Universities, 1941-1942 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Colleges and Universities - Requests, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Collier, C.F., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Committee on Discrimination in Employment, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Committee to Defend America by Aiding the Allies, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Common Council for American Unity, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Compulsory Savings, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Conference Board, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Congressional Daily, 1941-1942 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Congressional Intelligence, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Congressional Secretaries Club, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Connecticut CIO News, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Connecticut Industrial Union Council, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Connally-May Amendments, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Connery, Lawrence, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Connolly, Eugene, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Connolly, John Jr., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Conscription Act, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Consumers, 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Consumer Action, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Consumer Income, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Consumers Union, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Coordinating Committee for Democratic Action, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Cottin, Louis M., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Coughlin, Charles E., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Council for Democracy, 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Crosby, Alexander L., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Davies, Joseph O., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Deatherage, George, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Delco and Frigidaire Campaign, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Department of Labor - Canada, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Dillon, P.J., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Discrimination, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Doering, G.E., 1941 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Domestic Service, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Dooley, C.R., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Dowling, Allen, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Dowling, John, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Dowling - Lefax, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Dowling, Mrs. Lyle, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Dreiser, Theodore, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Driscoll, John J., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Earnshaw, Kirk, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Eastern Sociological Society, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Eastman, Buford, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Economic Notes, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Economic Outlook, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Edison, Inc., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Editor and Publisher, 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Education - Books, undated (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Education - Commercial Material, 1939-1941 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Education Work, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Edwards, L.P., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Eggleston, Arthur, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Einhorn, Nat, 1939-1941 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Elconin, William B., 1941 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Electrical industry- Cartels, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Electrical industry- Employment and Production, 1937-1941 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Electrical industry- G.E. and Westinghouse Special Report, undated (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Electrical industry- G.E. and Westinghouse Special Report, undated (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Electrical industry- Radio, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Electrical industry- Sickness, undated (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Electrical industry- Wages, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - "Electrical World", 1941 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Electro-Voice Campaign, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Espionage Act, undated (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Facts on File, Inc., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Falconer, Douglas P., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Federated Press, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Films, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Fitzpatrick, Michael, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Fleisher, Henry, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Fleming, Col. Philip, undated (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Flynn, Al, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Flynn, Edward, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Food, 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Ford Contract, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Fortune Magazine, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Fowler, C.W., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Friday, Inc., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Gandall, William, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - General Electric, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - General Electric-Report to Members on Wage Question, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - General Motors-Public Relations, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - General Motors-War Labor Board Case, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Gilman, Beryl, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Gleason, Leverett, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Goldsborough, Anna, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Goldstein, Frances, 1939-40 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Goodelman, Leon, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Gordon, Dave, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Gore, Bill, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Gould, Joseph, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Government Printing Office, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - "Great Bus Strike", 1941 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Green, John, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Green, William, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Greenfield, Sam, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Grimes, Conrad, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Group Insurance, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Guild Reporter, undated (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Guthrie, Robert, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Haessler, Carl, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Hague Case, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Halifax, Lord, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Hammond, John, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Hansman, George, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Hapsburg, Otto, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Hard, William, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Hardie, Mrs. Clarene, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Harley, Hugh, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Harris, Reed, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Hart, Mervin K., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Harvard University, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Haskett, L.G., 1941 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Haug, Fred, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Hay-Adams House, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Haywood, Allen, 1939-1941 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Health, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Heath, S. Burton, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Hearst, William Randolph, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Hein, August, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Henderson, Leon, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Hendly, Charles, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Herrick, Elinore, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Hetzel, Ralph, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - High Cost of Living, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - High Cost of Living, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - High Cost of Living, 1941-1942 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Highlander Folk School, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Hillman, Sidney, 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Hobbs, Bill, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Hoffman, Clare, 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Hollenbeck, Dan, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Hopkins, Harry, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Hospital Plans, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Hotels - Unionized, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Housing, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Housing Act, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - How to Speak Effectively, undated (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - Howard Clothes, undated (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Huberman, Leo, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - Hudson, Frank, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 177)
  - Hughes, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 178)
  - Hull, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - Hunter, William, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - Hutchenson, William, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 181)
  - Hymowitz, Harry, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 182)
  - "In Fact", 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Income Certificate Plan, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - India News, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Industrial Fatigue, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Inflation, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Information Brief, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Insurance, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - International Fur and Leather Union, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - International Juridical Association, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - International Labor Defense, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - International Labor Office, 1939-1941 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - International Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers Union, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Investigating Committees, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Iowa, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Isserman, Abe, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Jablonowski, E., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Jackson, C.S., 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Jackson, Gardner, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Jackson, Robert, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Jeremias, Siegmund, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Johnson, Harold, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Kamp, Joseph, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Kaufman, I., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Kaufman, Milton, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Kennedy, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Kielzeski, Josephine, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Kieran, James, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - King, James V., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - King, Jerome, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - King, William, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Kirkwood, Robert, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Kittner, Lilian, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Klausner, Rachel, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Ku Klux Klan, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Labor Research Association, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - LaFollette Farm Labor Bills, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Labor Herald, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 37)